<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Alex Dunn has no idea what he’s doing</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Alex Dunn has no idea what he’s doing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://garbage.world/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>homebrew-emacs</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/homebrew-emacs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/homebrew-emacs/</guid><description>Homebrew is an OS X package manager primarily focused on installing command-line tools, but you can import external collections of package formulae called “taps”. I forked Eric Davis’ tap of Emacs packages and expanded it, and I now use it instead of package.el and MELPA. It still doesn’t have as many packages as MELPA does, but you can help fix that!</description></item><item><title>Twitter bots</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/bots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/bots/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve made enough Twitter bots now that I guess it&amp;rsquo;s something I can link to here. Follow them, or don&amp;rsquo;t, or follow just the good ones? (Are there any good ones?)</description></item><item><title>&lt;em&gt;Modern Philosophy&lt;/em&gt; in plain text</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/modphil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/modphil/</guid><description>Modern Philosophy is a free textbook created by Walter Ott. It combines public-domain primary sources with supplementary material and study questions. Everything not in the public domain is licensed under CC BY-NC-SA 3.0.
This modified version of the text is written in Markdown. Markdown is a plain-text syntax that allows for easy conversion to other file formats. Using pandoc, Modern Philosophy can be easily converted to HTML, PDF, EPUB, and many other formats.</description></item></channel></rss>