<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>what is going on</title><link>http://garbage.world/</link><description>Recent content on what is going on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://garbage.world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WordPreSSL</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/wordpressl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/wordpressl/</guid><description>This is an Ansible playbook for provisioning a CentOS server with an SSL-enabled WordPress installation. The original motivation was to be able to quickly set up websites for friends and associates in the spirit of Brianna Laugher’s “Playing Sysadmin for my Activist Mates”. Feedback, testing, and pull requests are all very welcome.</description></item><item><title>homebrew-emacs</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/homebrew-emacs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/homebrew-emacs/</guid><description>Homebrew is an OS X package manager primarily focused on installing command-line tools, but you can import external collections of package formulae called “taps”. I forked Eric Davis’ tap of Emacs packages and expanded it, and I now use it instead of package.el and MELPA. It still doesn’t have as many packages as MELPA does, but you can help fix that!</description></item><item><title>Not Svbtle</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/svbtle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/svbtle/</guid><description>I spent three years in the Philosophy Department at UCSB, and used my Svbtle blog to write about the highs and lows of academic philosophy, on such subjects as racism, sexism, ableism, and that famous law professor we all know who sends threats of legal action to people who make fun of him online.</description></item><item><title>company-emoji.el</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/company-emoji/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/company-emoji/</guid><description>If you use Emacs, you’re a big ’ol nerd. But you can still pretend to be cool by using emoji like the teens and moms do. All it takes is company-mode and company-emoji.el. Install them both (using MELPA or Homebrew or manually), then add something like this to your emacs.el:
(require &amp;#39;company-emoji) (add-to-list &amp;#39;company-backends &amp;#39;company-emoji) Then B💥💥M.</description></item><item><title>UCSB Philosophy</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/ucsb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/ucsb/</guid><description>The University of California, Santa Barbara has a Philosophy department, and the Philosophy department has a website. In 2014 I rewrote the website from the ground up (twice!), making it modern, responsive, and accessible.</description></item><item><title>libgen.js</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/libgen.js/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/libgen.js/</guid><description>libgen is a Node.js wrapper for the Library Genesis API, with search added on top of it. Install it in the root folder of your project with npm install libgen, then require it where it&amp;rsquo;s needed:
var libgen = require(&amp;#39;libgen&amp;#39;); Your application then has access to search, random texts, and other methods.</description></item><item><title>How to Add Needless Complexity to Your Life</title><link>http://garbage.world/posts/email/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/posts/email/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I used Apple Mail forever until recently, when my Exchange account
starting causing it to blow itself up.  Instead of installing
Thunderbird and moving on with my life, I decided it was a good idea
to start being a Serious Email User, and so I installed the Serious
Email Client &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mutt.org&#34;&gt;mutt&lt;/a&gt;.  But since this is a piece
of Serious Software, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t any easy-to-find, good documentation
focused on actually &lt;em&gt;sending and receiving email&lt;/em&gt; as opposed to
Installing and Configuring mutt.  (Even
&lt;a href=&#34;http://curvedthoughts.com/blog/email-using-getmail-msmtp-mutt/&#34; title=&#34;Manage email using getmail, msmtp, and mutt&#34;&gt;the hard-to-find ones&lt;/a&gt; didn&amp;rsquo;t go in-depth
enough, and weren&amp;rsquo;t written for OS X.)  So this my attempt to get
everything necessary—and nothing more—written down in one place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Library Genesis API</title><link>http://garbage.world/posts/libgen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/posts/libgen/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://libgen.io/&#34;&gt;Library Genesis&lt;/a&gt; has an API, but the only
documentation is
&lt;a href=&#34;http://genofond.org/viewtopic.php?p=39355&#34; title=&#34;The Library Genesis Miner&#39;s Hut&#34;&gt;a forum thread in Russian&lt;/a&gt;.  So this is an English-language
guide to using the LibGen API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I don&amp;rsquo;t know Russian, and had to read the original thread using
&lt;a href=&#34;https://translate.google.com/translate?hl=en&amp;amp;sl=auto&amp;amp;tl=en&amp;amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fgenofond.org%2Fviewtopic.php%3Fp%3D39355&#34;&gt;Google Translate&lt;/a&gt;,
so corrections and additions are very welcome!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Twitter bots</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/bots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/bots/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve made enough Twitter bots now that I guess it&amp;rsquo;s something I can link to here. Follow them, or don&amp;rsquo;t, or follow just the good ones? (Are there any good ones?)</description></item><item><title>Baruffio</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/baruffio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/baruffio/</guid><description>Baruffio is a blog for people who take silly things way too seriously. It&amp;rsquo;s where you can read ludicrously in-depth analyses of a single spell. It&amp;rsquo;s where the only argument against a conspiracy theory is that it&amp;rsquo;s not consistent. It&amp;rsquo;s where we&amp;rsquo;re still talking about Harry Potter, after all these years.</description></item><item><title>Exists.js</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/exists.js/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/exists.js/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a scumbag analytic philosopher like me then this might actually come in handy, like when your &amp;ldquo;friend&amp;rdquo; suggests that chairs are ontologically innocent.</description></item><item><title>Cultural Appropriation at Lucidity</title><link>http://garbage.world/posts/lucidity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/posts/lucidity/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt; (1 August 2013): Jonah Haas has published
  &lt;a href=&#34;http://lucidityfestival.com/reframing-the-cultural-appropriation-conversation-towards-synergy-co-learning-and-peace/&#34; title=&#34;Reframing the cultural appropriation conversation towards synergy,
  co-learning, and peace&#34;&gt;a reply on the Lucidity blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santa Barbara-based &lt;a href=&#34;http://lucidityfestival.com/&#34; title=&#34;Lucidity Festival website&#34;&gt;Lucidity Festival&lt;/a&gt; has a problem with cultural
appropriation.  Unfortunately, the organizers don&amp;rsquo;t seem to have a
firm grasp on what &amp;lsquo;cultural appropriation&amp;rsquo; means, and so they don&amp;rsquo;t
see what the big deal is or why they should make changes to their
festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Reading.js</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/reading/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/reading/</guid><description>Reading.js is a crummy bit of CSS and JavaScript that&amp;rsquo;s supposed to make it easier to read long documents online. (Like this one!)
Include two lines in the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; of a plain HTML file&amp;mdash;the kind produced by pandoc or by most Markdown-to-HTML converters&amp;mdash;and gain nifty features like keyboard shortcuts, section folding, and color scheme switching:
&amp;lt;linkrel=&amp;quot;stylesheet&amp;quot;href=&amp;quot;http://baruffio.com/reading.js/stylesheets/reading.css&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;scripttype=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot;src=&amp;quot;http://baruffio.com/reading.js/scripts/reading.min.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; </description></item><item><title>Students for Justice in Palestine at UC Berkeley</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/sjp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/sjp/</guid><description>The Berkeley chapter of Students for Justice in Palestine is &amp;ldquo;a group of students, faculty, and community members working together at the University of California, Berkeley, in solidarity with the struggle of the indigenous Palestinian people against apartheid and occupation.&amp;rdquo;
In July of 2012, I redesigned their website, http://calsjp.org, making it more accessible (especially for mobile devices) and more maintainable.</description></item><item><title>Fountain CLM</title><link>http://garbage.world/things/fountain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/things/fountain/</guid><description>Codeless Language Modules (CLMs) are plugins for TextWrangler and BBEdit that add syntax highlighting, code folding, and other capabilities for languages not natively supported by these programs.
Fountain is a plain-text syntax for writing screenplays. (The Fountain syntax is similar to that of Markdown, a general-purpose syntax.) Fountain files are designed to be very readable, but they can be easily converted to other formats (like PDF and FDX) using Fountain-compatible applications.</description></item><item><title>&lt;em&gt;Modern Philosophy&lt;/em&gt; in plain text</title><link>http://garbage.world/projects/modphil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/projects/modphil/</guid><description>Modern Philosophy is a free textbook created by Walter Ott. It combines public-domain primary sources with supplementary material and study questions. Everything not in the public domain is licensed under CC BY-NC-SA 3.0.
This modified version of the text is written in Markdown. Markdown is a plain-text syntax that allows for easy conversion to other file formats. Using pandoc, Modern Philosophy can be easily converted to HTML, PDF, EPUB, and many other formats.</description></item><item><title>Sacrifices</title><link>http://garbage.world/stories/sacrifices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/stories/sacrifices/</guid><description>A hip new version of Judith Jarvis Thomson&amp;rsquo;s violinist thought experiment. Maybe a little more realistic. But probably no more convincing.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Smith Goes to the Hospital</title><link>http://garbage.world/stories/smith/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/stories/smith/</guid><description>A super sad story about Bernard Williams and utilitarianism. The moral is that you really just shouldn&amp;rsquo;t bother visiting your friend in the hospital.</description></item></channel></rss>