<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Websites on Alex Dunn has no idea what he’s doing</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/</link><description>Recent content in Websites on Alex Dunn has no idea what he’s doing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://garbage.world/websites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Not Svbtle</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/svbtle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/svbtle/</guid><description>I spent three years in the Philosophy Department at UCSB, and used my Svbtle blog to write about the highs and lows of academic philosophy, on such subjects as racism, sexism, ableism, and that famous law professor we all know who sends threats of legal action to people who make fun of him online.</description></item><item><title>UCSB Philosophy</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/ucsb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/ucsb/</guid><description>The University of California, Santa Barbara has a Philosophy department, and the Philosophy department has a website. In 2014 I rewrote the website from the ground up (twice!), making it modern, responsive, and accessible.</description></item><item><title>Baruffio</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/baruffio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/baruffio/</guid><description>Baruffio is a blog for people who take silly things way too seriously. It&amp;rsquo;s where you can read ludicrously in-depth analyses of a single spell. It&amp;rsquo;s where the only argument against a conspiracy theory is that it&amp;rsquo;s not consistent. It&amp;rsquo;s where we&amp;rsquo;re still talking about Harry Potter, after all these years.</description></item><item><title>Students for Justice in Palestine at UC Berkeley</title><link>http://garbage.world/websites/sjp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://garbage.world/websites/sjp/</guid><description>The Berkeley chapter of Students for Justice in Palestine is &amp;ldquo;a group of students, faculty, and community members working together at the University of California, Berkeley, in solidarity with the struggle of the indigenous Palestinian people against apartheid and occupation.&amp;rdquo;
In July of 2012, I redesigned their website, http://calsjp.org, making it more accessible (especially for mobile devices) and more maintainable.</description></item></channel></rss>